[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Episode 11]
You're awake.
The examination results show that you're fine.
It's just a mild concussion.
Do you feel any other discomfort?
I'm a little dizzy.
I see. Dizziness is normal.
As long as you don't feel too nauseous,
it's not a big problem.
Rest well.
Doctor.
I feel like my memory is a little blurry.
I can't remember what happened in the last six months.
Your memory?
Judging from the scans,
the memory area doesn't seem to be damaged.
However, the human brain is a mysterious thing.
Severe shock or trauma can both affect your memory.
Maybe you'll recover after some rest.
But to be honest, given your current condition,
there's no effective treatment right now.
Shen Mo.
Shen Mo, open the door!
You're Shen Mo, right?
Yes.
I only rented this place to you so cheaply
because I saw how hard it was for a fresh graduate.
I can't believe I trusted you.
Look at how much rent you owe.
This is going too far.
I'm sorry.
I injured my hand a while ago,
and I haven't been able to find a job.
Can you give me a few more days?
How much more can I accommodate you?
Pack up your things.
You need to move out.
Please, just give me a little more time.
I can't move out yet. I'm still waiting...
Enough. Don't say another word.
You have two days to pack your things.
I'll be back in two days to take the house back.
Hurry it up!
Wait.
What is it, Mr. Ji?
Drive forward a little more.
Stop here.
It sounds beautiful.
Then I'll sing it for you often, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Stop.
Shen Mo.
I want to see you.
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I have the wrong person.
Oh, it's okay.
Do you know where the previous tenant went?
I'm not sure.
I heard the landlord mention it once.
I think he left because he couldn't pay the rent.
I see.
So...
In the end, I'm still homeless.
Drop everything you're doing.
Find Shen Mo for me.
Now!
Yes. I'm from T University's Department of Fine Arts.
But I might not be able to paint now.
However, I can do anything else.
All right. Thank you.
Who is it?
Mr. Ji.
How do you know I live here?
You...
You remember who I am?
You're Ji An An's brother.
Back then,
didn't you pay for my medical bills after my accident?
Speaking of which, I really must thank you.
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't have known how to pay those bills.
Don't just stand there. Come in.
Please, come in.
I'm sorry, my place...
It's indeed a bit shabby.
I haven't really tidied up.
Here, have a seat.
How did you end up like this?
My hand was injured, remember?
I haven't been able to find a job.
I'm way behind on rent,
so I'm just staying here for now.
Take this for now.
No, I can't.
I already owe you a huge favor for my medical bills.
If you give me more money...
First, I won't be able to pay you back,
and second, I'd be too ashamed to take it.
Just take it.
You don't have to pay me back.
No, really.
I'm able-bodied.
I can earn money anywhere.
Besides, I'm only here temporarily.
It may look shabby, but it's actually not that bad.
Fine, you don't have to take it.
How about this?
Pack your things and come with me.
I'll arrange a place for you to stay.
You can move out once you've made money.
I appreciate your kindness, really.
I don't know why you're being so nice to me,
but I really can't accept all this.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
Oh.
I see.
What if I give you a job?
It's not charity, nor is it an ordinary job.
Would you be willing to do it?
Is this the power of the Ji family?
Take a look.
What is this?
Be my lover.
What?
Be my contract lover.
What you're holding is the contract.
Me?
A contract lover?
You and Zhou Yang had a past.
I don't trust you, nor do I trust Zhou Yang.
To ensure Zhou Yang stays with my sister,
and to make him give up on you,
the best way is to keep an eye on you.
And the best way to do that is to keep you by my side
as my lover.
And I can also use you
to ward off the advances of some boring guys out there.
Everyone wins.
I... I don't think this is a good idea.
Do you have an objection?
You'll get your share of benefits.
It's all clearly stated in the contract.
If you have any requests, feel free to ask.
That's not what I meant.
Then what do you mean?
I already owe Mr. Ji so much.
He wants to ensure his sister's happiness by doing this.
I...
I'm just a homeless, useless person.
What right do I have to refuse?
Besides... Zhou Yang...
Fine.
Since I'm the redundant one,
I might as well sell myself for a good price.
You'll live here from now on.
You can pick any room you like.
Once you've chosen a room, go take a shower.
This "lover" role...
It's just a title, right?
Mr. Ji shouldn't want to do anything to me, right?
He probably won't.
I'm sure he's not interested in me.
But... if he wants to,
I can't really refuse, can I?
After all, I've signed the contract.
My body...
should be included
in this lover's contract, right?
Come here.
Take off your clothes.
You haven't even dried yourself off.
We signed a contract, didn't we?
So, we're lovers now, right?
Yeah.
Take it off.
Call my name...
Mr. Ji.
Call me "Ming Xuan".
Ming Xuan.
Louder.
Mr. Ji is so experienced.
He must despise my poor performance.
Oh, Shen Mo...
You're not even qualified to be his outlet.
Mr. Ji.
Breakfast is ready.
I'll skip breakfast.
I have an urgent meeting to attend.
Open it.
This is...
A ring I had my secretary buy.
We have to play the part fully.
I didn't expect Mr. Ji to lie.
This clearly isn't a new ring.
A big boss like him...
And he can't even afford a new ring?
I'm off to work.
Why does it fit so well?
[Four years later]
Since An An's accident,
Mr. Ji has been gone for four years.
Ironically,
I was Mr. Ji's contract lover for three years.
It wasn't until the day he left...
that I remembered everything at Jinxiu Mountain Villa.
Oh, boss.
Slacking off again?
Sorry.
I'm back late.
I didn't delay your date with your partner, did I?
I wonder which of us is the boss.
I feel like I care more about the studio than you do.
Oh, please.
It's true, though.
In a blink, you're a senior employee.
Four years. Time flies.
Exactly.
I've been here since the studio opened.
I wanted some peace and quiet,
but I didn't expect it to be this quiet.
But then again, it's been four years.
I've never seen you date anyone.
Boss, you're already 30.
You should start dating.
I'll only be 29 after the New Year.
It's the same thing.
Listen.
The older you get,
the less popular you are in the dating market.
Where did you learn that from?
Come on, I'm being serious.
Do you want me to set you up with someone?
- Actually, I have a college classmate... - Stop right there.
No, thanks.
What?
Is there someone in your heart?
Someone you've been waiting for in silence?
Did you lock your heart away after a breakup?
Was it your first love?
- Yes. - Or was it a secret crush?
Oh! A goddess you've pursued for years?
No. Stop guessing.
Boss, my guy is here to pick me up.
I'm heading out. Bye!
Go on.
Boss, I believe you'll definitely win over that person.
Good luck!
I painted so many works over those years.
That person must have put in so much effort
to collect them all.
[Calendar 2026]
I'm going away for a bit next week.
I'll leave the studio to you.
Boss, are you going on a trip again?
You get to go away every year at this time.
I'm so jealous.
What do you mean "trip"?
I'm going out to find inspiration.
Artists need inspiration to paint.
Then when will you let me go out to find some inspiration too,
my dear boss?
Fine. I'll give you your annual leave when I get back.
How's that?
Really? It's a deal then.
My dear boss, where are you going this time?
Where are you looking for inspiration?
The usual place.
M Island again?
That's a honeymoon destination.
Couples go there together, okay?
You're a lifelong bachelor.
Why do you go there every year?
Looking for a fling, or trying to steal someone's partner?
I wonder what's going on in that head of yours every day.
I told you, I'm looking for inspiration.
You go there every spring.
I don't believe there isn't a special reason.
What special reason could there be?
"The whole year's work depends on a good start in spring."
Everything awakens in spring.
It's the best time to go out.
"The whole year's work depends on a good start in spring."
Boss, I think you're just in heat.
I think you don't want your salary anymore.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry!
I'm sorry, boss.
Please be magnanimous.
- Forgive my insolence. - Go on.
Get back to work.
Slave driver.
It's been four years.
The days have just passed by like this.
I used to yearn for a life like this.
At this very moment four years ago,
if those things hadn't happened,
I would've gone to M Island with Ji Ming Xuan.
Maybe we were just never meant to be.
[VIP Passage]
This way, please.
Welcome to SEAMO Hotel.
This is your room.
Our hotel's investor is also Chinese.
So, in the overall design of the hotel,
there are many of his own designs.
We hope to provide you with an experience like home.
If you have any needs, please feel free to contact me.
Enjoy your stay.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Mr. Ji.
Where are you?
Where are you looking at the moon now?
Ming Xuan.
Ming Xuan, come here quickly.
Coming!
Let's go over there.
Okay.
I wonder how Ji Ming Xuan is doing now.
Has he changed at all?
But... I probably won't see him again in this lifetime.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Ji.
Come with me.
Mr. Ji, that's enough.
Rinse it a bit longer.
You haven't changed much.
Neither have you, Mr. Ji.
Come to my room first.
I'll go get you some medicine.
I'm on vacation on M Island.
I've started painting again.
I came here to find some inspiration.
Are you here alone?
Yes.
I'm the only one with free time.
When did you arrive?
A few days ago.
What about you?
I've been here for a while.
There, all done.
Thanks.
Young Master.
Daddy!
Speak Chinese.
Dad!
Come here.
Say hello to Mr. Shen.
Hello, sir.
Hello there.
What's your name?
Ji Ning.
Hello, Xiao Ning.
How old are you this year?
You're three?
Sir, play with me.
Be good.
His hand is hurt.
Chen.
Young Master, let's go out and play.
Bye, sir.
Are you here on vacation too, Mr. Ji?
I'm here for business.
There was no one to look after Ji Ning,
so I brought him along.
I see.
I didn't know you were married, Mr. Ji.
Congratulations.
And you?
Did you get back together with Zhou Yang?
We haven't seen each other in years.
- Oh, I thought... - When are you...
Daddy!
It's getting late.
I should head back now.
Go and tend to your son.
Go back to your room.
Let's have dinner tonight.
I have to paint in the evenings.
I hate being interrupted when I'm inspired.
Tomorrow, then.
Okay.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Thank you.
Mr. Ji sent this for you.
He specifically asked you to change your dressing.
Oh.
Thank you.
[Apply the medication every two hours until the swelling subsides.]
Mr. Ji...
He's still the same as before.
Daddy.
Why aren't you asleep yet?
Xiao Ning.
Because I thought of someone...
Someone I've known for a very long time.
Do you miss him, Daddy?
Whether I miss him or not, it's all in the past now.
Xiao Ning, time for bed.
Be good.
Okay.
Ji Ming Xuan...
I once held that person's heart,
but in the end, I let go.
If I'd remembered those six months sooner,
would things have been different?
Forget it.
Some people and some things,
once missed, are gone forever.
Hello, Yang Yue.
What's up, boss?
Why are you calling me so early?
Any orders for me?
I forgot about the time difference.
Help me book a ticket.
I'm going back.
Remember to tidy up the studio.
Huh? Why are you planning to return early?
There's no need to stay any longer.
Did something... upset you?
No.
Quite the opposite.
I'm too happy.
So... it's enough.